Whistler: 25 seconds left...
98: Well, it's been fun.
Longhorn: We’ll join you guys later there.
98: Yep.
98: Thanks for everything!
2000: Same to you guys!
98: Ready, ME?
ME: More than ever.
2000: See you soon!
XP: We'll miss you guys.
98: See you!
98: Goodbye, world!
2000: Sigh.
2000: I guess this really is goodbye.
Whistler: Yeah...
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I’ve never seen a silver lining in this.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: They really shined it for us.
2000: Yeah, I agree.
Whistler: It’s inevitable.
XP: Well, we'll meet them eventually.
2000: Yeah.
2000: Alright, let’s give our words.
2000: Thank you, 98 and ME.
Whistler: Thank you for all the great works.
XP: We hope your works cherish.
Whistler: The persistence, the dedication…
Whistler: Let everyone learn from them.
2000: We're going to miss you two.
2000: A bientôt, tous les deux...
95: Alright, we're here now!
Chicago: Hey, finally!
Chicago: Let's go to the entrance.
98: Huh?
98: Where am I?
98: Wait...
98: ME!
ME: Ugh, what?
ME: Wait…
98: We’re in heaven!!
ME: Wait, what?!
ME: We made it!
98: Oh, indeed we did!
95: Greetings!
Chicago: Welcome to heaven!
98: Wait...
98: Is that you, 95?!
95: Indeed it is!
98: And Chicago?
Chicago: Yep!
ME: Long time no see!
98: Yeah, it's been so long!
Chicago: Sure has been.
95: Looks like you made it!
98: Indeed we have, am I right?
ME: Agreed.
Chicago: Also, we’d like to give you two a tour!
98: Oh, for sure!
ME: This is gonna be exciting.
ME: Heaven here we come!
95: Alright then, let’s go!
98: Wow!
98: This place is like a palace.
95: I know, right?
95: I got that first impression too.
ME: Except it's all nature!
Chicago: Yeah...
Chicago: We’re in Ballmer Valley right now.
Chicago: There's endless more regions.
98: Woah , who built this?
95: Hey, that’s my house!
98: Wait, what?
ME: Looks fitting!
95: Chicago and I built this.
Chicago: Yep.
98: Oh wow.
98: I like the blend-in.
98: How much did it cost?
95: Well, about a few thousand dollars.
98: You're kidding!
98: How?
95: Don’t you remember?
95: Things are discounted here!
98: Oh, right!
ME: I’m not surprised, I like that!
Chicago: Haha.
Chicago: Well, we have free houses.
Chicago: Most of them have similar designs.
98: Oh well.
ME: Things have been amazing so far!
95: Well, it's heaven!
95: Things are crazy here.
98: Should we settle at the free houses for now?
95: Yep, that works.
95: Wait, how about we go do that first?
98: Yeah, sounds good!
ME: I agree.
95: I’ll register your names.
95: Chicago, can you guide?
Chicago: Sure thing!
95: Alright.
Chicago: Here we are!
ME: Woah.
98: Literature!
ME: That’s a ton of books.
Chicago: Yeah.
Chicago: Sometimes there’s those, too.
ME: I bet 98's keen of that.
ME: He reads a lot.
98: Haha, yeah.
Chicago: This is the living room, by the way.
98: Ah.
98: What about the dining room?
Chicago: Let’s go check.
98: I like the atmosphere.
ME: Yeah, I can tell.
Chicago: I have the feeling that 95 built this.
Chicago: He knows a lot about architecture.
98: Yeah, figures.
98: Hmm, typical bedroom.
ME: Cool stuff.
98: I gotta say, this is a really nice house!
98: Might just go with this one.
Chicago: Maybe!
Chicago: Well, we have a lot more around.
98: True.
ME: Should we go to a different house now?
98: Good idea.
Chicago: Alright then.
ME: Looks different!
Chicago: I forgot to mention the themes differ.
ME: Ah.
ME: It looks more generic.
98: I thought the same, haha.
Chicago: Wait a second...
Chicago: This is the house I lived in before!
ME: Wait, what?
98: Seriously?
Chicago: Yeah!
Chicago: Back when everyone just arrived.
98: Woah.
98: I can't imagine you lived here!
Chicago: Haha!
Chicago: Things weren’t ready like now.
ME: Yeah, this is very generic.
98: I still can’t believe you lived here, Chicago.
Chicago: You don’t say.
Chicago: Not a house for me here!
98: ME has the props for this.
ME: You bet!
ME: So far this is my liking.
Chicago: Yeah, I thought so!
98: I prefer a different kind of house.
98: If you know what I mean.
Chicago: Haha, me too.
ME: You guys are crazy.
ME: While I relax at a plain house…
98: Probably 'cause we're enthusiasts…
ME: Haha.
Chicago: Alright, let's check the storage room.
95: Welp, that's all the houses!
Chicago: What do you guys think?
98: I love the budget manners!
ME: Same.
ME: Out of the ten houses, I prefer the second.
Chicago: I knew you'd go for that, haha.
98: I think I'll go with the first.
98: It's a lot more convenient.
95: Sure thing.
95: So then, it’s settled?
98: As is!
ME: Yep!
95: D'accord.
Chicago: Bienvenue de paradis!
98: Merci beaucoup!
Chicago: Alright, I’ll put the stuff up on record.
Chicago: Where should we go meanwhile?
95: Hmm…
95: It's afternoon.
ME: Oh yeah.
98: Well, I’m getting hungry.
98: I suppose we could go eat.
95: Where should we go?
Chicago: Hmm, what about Allen Meals?
ME: Oh?
95: Ah, good thinking.
98: Is it a restaurant?
Chicago: Yep, it's really good too.
98: Well, I'm all for it.
ME: Me too.
Chicago: Alright then.
Chicago: I’ll meet you guys later!
95: See you!
95: Welcome to Allard Bay!
98: Woah.
98: This is cool!
95: The town's been under construction.
95: It’s a dedication to Microsoft.
ME: I like that.
95: Also, the restaurant's right there.
98: Alright.
OS X Public Beta: Hello, guests!
OS X Public Beta: Wait...
98: Beta?!
OS X Public Beta: 98?!
OS X Public Beta: And ME?!
ME: Yep, that's us!
95: Looks like you met some friends!
OS X Public Beta: Yeah! I wasn't informed.
95: Sorry!
OS X Public Beta: Nah, it's fine.
OS X Public Beta: Well, what'd you guys like to order?
98: Hmm...
98: I'm gonna get a salad.
ME: I'll get a small sized pizza.
95: And I'll get a regular burger.
OS X Public Beta: Got it.
OS X Public Beta: Three orders coming up!
98: Thanks!
OS X Public Beta: No problem.
95: Great, let's get our seats.
98: Welp, off we wait!
95: The service here is quite fast.
98: Cool.
ME: I can’t wait for my first meal!
98: Same here!
95: You won’t expect it!
Chicago: Hey guys, I'm back.
95: Wait, we forgot to order yours.
Chicago: How could you, 95?
Chicago: Haha.
95: Whoops.
Chicago: I'll go get my order.
95: So, how's heaven so far?
98: It's been amazing.
98: And I see familiar OSes.
ME: Yeah, really.
95: Good to hear!
95: There aren't many here, though.
95: Construction's laid back a little.
98: Makes sense.
98: XP’s impatient about new OSes.
95: Haha, thought he would!
Chicago: Alright, I'm back!
Chicago: What'd I miss?
95: Just talking about life.
Chicago: You ought to!
Chicago: Also, I just ordered a salad.
98: Nice!
OS X Public Beta: Here's to you two!
98: Thanks!
ME: Thanks to you!
OS X Public Beta: No problem.
OS X Public Beta: More food coming up!
98: That was fast.
95: Told you!
Chicago: You'll get used to it.
OS X Public Beta: And here's another.
95: Merci!
Chicago: Thank you!
OS X Public Beta: You're welcome!
OS X Public Beta: Also, mind if I sit here?
Chicago: Yeah, no problem.
OS X Public Beta: Alright.
98: Well, first meal in heaven!
ME: Woohoo!
98: Shall we eat now?
95: Of course!
98: Delicious!
ME: I know right!
95: I agree.
OS X Public Beta: Alright, I'm back.
OS X Public Beta: How's the food, by the way?
95: Great as always!
Chicago: Agreed.
98: Really good!
ME: It's by far the best I've had.
OS X Public Beta: Thanks, guys!
98: You're welcome.
OS X Public Beta: So, how was it on the earth?
OS X Public Beta: I haven't been there for long.
98: Well? Not too bad.
98: I had a lot of jobs, though.
ME: Yeah, me too.
98: I did learn a cool thing, though.
OS X Public Beta: Oh?
OS X Public Beta: What is it?
98: You'll never guess it...
98: Fluent French!
95: Woah, what?!
Chicago: Woah!
OS X Public Beta: Wait, what?!
ME: It's by far the best I've had.
98: Yeah, I haven't told you all yet.
98: 2000 and I went overseas.
Chicago: Oh wow.
95: For how long?
98: Hmm, for about 2 years.
95: Nice!
ME: I've been researching stuff.
ME: Mainly about Windows projects.
Chicago: Cool!
Chicago: What's it about?
ME: It's about the Longhorn project.
Chicago: Ah.
OS X Public Beta: Cool name!
OS X Public Beta: What took them so long, though?
Chicago: Well, it's a long story.
Chicago: I could go in depth another time.
OS X Public Beta: Sure, haha.
ME: Wait, that reminds me.
ME: Where's everyone else?
95: Wait…
Chicago: Oh, right! I almost forgot.
Chicago: They’re all in Kernel.
98: Kernel?
95: We’ve been preparing something special.
98: What is it?
95: Oh, you'll see!
95: We’ve been preparing something special.
ME: Wait, what?!
98: You serious?
Chicago: Yep!
Chicago: Beta Mac, you’re invited too.
OS X Public Beta: Really?
95: We’re leaving at 7 o’clock by train.
95: Do you think you can make it?
OS X Public Beta: Concur.
OS X Public Beta: I close my restaurant soon.
95: Alright. Should we go now?
OS X Public Beta: Sure.
OS X Public Beta: See you!
98: Thanks, Beta!
OS X Public Beta: No problem!
98: Really good lunch today.
98: Thanks, guys.
ME: Yeah!
95: Hey, no problem.
Chicago: Beta Mac's good at cooking.
ME: I agree.
98: Well, what do we do now?
95: Hmm, we haven’t finished the tour.
95: We'll have to prepare in a few hours time.
98: Right.
98: Let’s continue, then!
95: Sure.
95: Well, that's it for now!
98: That was picturesque!
ME: Thanks for the tour, 95.
95: No problem.
Chicago: Well, this place is extensive.
Chicago: And it's only been several years!
98: Yet the nature never fails.
Chicago: Agreed.
ME: We should go prepare now.
ME: The sun's about to set.
98: ME, we don't have anything.
ME: Oh, right.
Chicago: We’ll meet you at the entrance then.
Chicago: Probably at about half past 5.
95: That sounds good.
98: Alright.
98: See you soon!
1.0: Ah, bienvenue messeiurs!
98: Merci!
1.0: Wait...
95: That's 98 and ME!
1.0: Oh, nice!
1.0: Welcome to heaven!
98: Thanks!
ME: Thank you!
1.0: You're welcome.
95: That's 98 and ME!
1.0: D'accord.
1.0: Alright, you may go!
95: Merci!
98: Woah.
98: It's been a while since I've hopped on a train.
ME: Me neither.
ME: I've been sick for weeks!
OS X Public Beta: Welp, ought to enjoy this one!
OS X Public Beta: Especially since it's all nature.
95: Well, you said it!
95: This will be a fun ride.
95: Allons-y, everyone?
Chicago: Ouais!
98: Oui!
ME: Allons-y!
OS X Public Beta: Oui!